A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Antiparkinsonism Drugs" 7:22, Issue 161, 1965 March 12 (Box 86, Folder 10-13, Box 87, Folder 1)
- "A Note on Milligram Potency and Misleading Promotion" 7:24, Issue 161, 1965 March 12 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- "Lincocin" 7:25, Issue 162, 1965 March 26 (Box 87, Folder 3-5)
- "How to Use Potassium Supplements Without Causing Intestinal Injury" 7:26, Issue 162, 1965 March 26 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- "Norgesic" 7:27, Issue 162, 1965 March 26 (Box 87, Folder 7-8)
- "Aventyl, Amother Antidepressant" 7:29, Issue 163, 1976 May 4-14 (Box 87, Folder 9-10)
- "Immunologic, Bioassay and Hormone Pregnancy Tests" 7:31, Issue 163, 1965 April 9 (Box 87, Folder 11-12, Box 88, Folder 1-2)
- "Viodenum" 7:32, Issue 163, 1965 April 9 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- "Ultrasonic Therapy" 7:33, Issue 164, 1965 April 23 (Box 88, Folder 4-7)
- "Tests of Meprobamate Tablets" 7:34, Issue 164, 1965 April 23 (Box 88, Folder 8-9)
- "Meprobamate" 7:36, Issue 164, 1965 April 23 (Box 88, Folder 10-12)
- "Pregnancy and Other Contraindications to Smallpox Vaccination" 7:37, Issue 165, 1965 May 7 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- "Photosensitivity Reactions to Drugs" 7:38, Issue 165, 1965 May 7 (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
- "Emergency Drug Kits for Cardiac Arrest" 7:40, Issue 165, 1965 May 7 (Box 89, Folder 4-9)
- "Dactinomycin" 7:41, Issue 166, 1965 May 21 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- "Dimethyl Sulfoxide (DMSO) " 7:42, Issue 166, 1965 May 21 (Box 90, Folder 1-4)
- "Desipramine" 7:44, Issue 166, 1965 May 21 (Box 90, Folder 5-7)
- "Cuemid" 7:45, Issue 167, 1965 June 4 (Box 90, Folder 8-9)
- "Oral Prolonged-Action Drugs" 7:46, Issue 167, 1965 June 4 (Box 90, Folder 10-11, Box 91, Folder 1-2)
- "Didrex" 7:48, Issue 167, 1965 June 4 (Box 91, Folder 3-4)
- "Corticosteroids and Allergic Rhinitis" 7:49, Issue 168, 1965 June 18 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- "Vitamin E" 7:50, Issue 168, 1970 January 23-October 16 (Box 91, Folder 6-8)
- "Ipechar - A Poison Control Kit" 7:51, Issue 168, 1965 June 18 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- "Tegopen" 7:53, Issue 169, 1965 July 2 (Box 91, Folder 10-11, Box 92, Folder 1)
- "Estrogens During and After the Menopause" 7:54, Issue 169, 1965 July 2 (Box 92, Folder 2-5)
- "First Aid Transparent Splints" 7:56, Issue 169, 1965 July 2 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- "Small-Intestine Ulceration and Enteric-Coated Potassium Chloride" 7:57, Issue 170, 1965 July 16 (Box 92, Folder 7-8)
- "Measles Vaccines" 7:58, Issue 170, 1965 July 16 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- "Afrin and Other Nasal Decongestant Drugs" 7:60, Issue 170, 1965 July 16 (Box 92, Folder 10-11)
- "Uses and Toxicity of Antimicrobial Sulfonamides" 7:60, Issue 170, 1965 July 16 (Box 93, Folder 1-3)
- "Rabies" 7:63, Issue 171, 1965 July 30 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- "Placentography" 7:64, Issue 171, 1965 July 30 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- "Parenteral Water and Electrolyte Solutions" 7:65, Issue 172, 1965 August 13 (Box 93, Folder 6-9)
- "Principal Toxic, Allergic, and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Agents (Revised May 1967) " 7:69, Issue 173, August 27, 1965, 1967 May; 1965 August 27 (Box 93, Folder 10, Box 94, Folder 1-2)
- "Pre-Sate" 7:73, Issue 174, 1965 September 10 (Box 94, Folder 3-5)
- "Influenza Vaccines" 7:74, Issue 174, 1965 September 10 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- "Sequential Oral Contraceptives" 7:77, Issue 175, 1965 September 24 (Box 94, Folder 7-10)
- "Cardiac Pacemakers" 7:78, Issue 175, 1965 September 24 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
- "A Further Warning on DMSO" 7:80, Issue 175, 1965 September 24 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- "The Choice of Systemic Antimicrobial Agents" 7:81, Issue 176, 1965 October 8 (Box 95, Folder 4-12)
- "Indocin" 7:89, Issue 177, 1965 October 22 (Box 96, Folder 1-3)
- "Serax and Solacen" 7:93, Issue 178, 1965 November 5 (Box 96, Folder 4-8)
- "Drugs for Dysmenorrhea" 7:95, Issue 178, 1965 November 5 (Box 96, Folder 9-11, Box 97, Folder 1-2)
- "Corticosteroids and Immunization" 7:96, Issue 178, 1965 November 5 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- "Typhoid Vaccines" 7:97, Issue 179, 1965 November 19 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- "Diapulse" 7:98, Issue 179, 1965 November 19 (Box 97, Folder 5-6)
- "Jectofer and Imferon" 7:99, Issue 179, 1965 November 19 (Box 97, Folder 7-11)
- "Tinactin" 7:101, Issue 180, 1965 December 3 (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
- "Mucomyst and Other Agents for Reducing the Viscosity of Pulmonary Secretions" 7:102, Issue 180, 1965 December 3 (Box 98, Folder 3-7)
- "Gastrointestinal Pacing" 7:104, Issue 180, 1965 December 3 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- "Adactone-A and Aldactazide-A" 7:105, Issue 181, 1965 December 17 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
- "Griseofulvin Formulations" 7:106, Issue 181, 1965 December 17 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- "Pancreatic Enzymes in the Treatment of Pancreatic Insufficiency" 7:107, Issue 181, 1965 December 17 (Box 99, Folder 1-3)
- "Gold Therapy in Rheumatoid Arthritis" 7:109, Issue 182, 1965 December 31 (Box 99, Folder 4-5)
- "Glucocorticoids for Parenteral Administration" 7:111, Issue 182, 1965 December 31 (Box 99, Folder 6-8)
- "Repository Vitamin B12 Preparations" 8:1, Issue 183, 1966 January 14 (Box 99, Folder 9-10)
- "Vaccines for Respiratory Infections" 8:2, Issue 183, 1966 January 14 (Box 99, Folder 11, Box 100, Folder 1)
- "Vicks Formula 44 for Coughs" 8:3, Issue 183, 1966 January 14 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- "Is Peritrate Life-Sustaining? " 8:5, Issue 184, 1966 January 28 (Box 100, Folder 3-10)
- "Non-Narcotic Analgesics" 8:7, Issue 184, 1965 January 28 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
- "New Reports on Oral Contraceptives" 8:9, Issue 185, 1966 February 11 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- "Safeguard and Other Antibacterial Soaps" 8:10, Issue 185, 1966 February 11 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
- "Probenecid as an Aid to Penicillin Therapy" 8:11, Issue 185, 1966 February 11 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- "Warning Against Prolonged-Action Sulfonamides" 8:13, Issue 186, 1966 February 25 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- "Triavil and Etrafon" 8:14, Issue 186, 1966 February 25 (Box 101, Folder 9-10, Box 102, Folder 1)
- "Glucola and Gel-A-Dex for Oral Glucose Tolerance Tests" 8:16, Issue 186, 1966 February 25 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- "Immunization of Infants and Children" 8:17, Issue 187, 1966 March 11 (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
- "Parenteral Tetracyclines" 8:19, Issue 187, 1966 March 11 (Box 102, Folder 6-7)
- "Head and Shoulders" 8:20, Issue 187, 1966 March 11 (Box 102, Folder 8-9)
- "Cloxacillin (TegoPen) and Streptococcal Pharyngitis" 8:21, Issue 188, 1966 March 25 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- "Treatment of Acute Malaria" 8:22, Issue 188, 1966 March 25 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- "Disposable Enema Kits" 8:23, Issue 188, 1966 March 25 (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
- "Fluid Therapy of Shock" 8:25, Issue 189, 1966 April 8 (Box 103, Folder 6-7)
- "Persantin" 8:27, Issue 189, 1966 April 8 (Box 103, Folder 8-9)
- "Quaalude and Insomnia" 8:29, Issue 190, 1966 April 22 (Box 103, Folder 10, Box 104, Folder 1-5)
- "Anogenital Itching" 8:30, Issue 190, 1966 April 22 (Box 104, Folder 6-7)
- "Alkeran and Multiple Myeloma" 8:32, Issue 190, 1966 April 22 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- "Serum Concentration of Antimicrobial Agents" 8:33, Issue 191, 1966 May 6 (Box 104, Folder 9-10)
- "Lithium for Manic States" 8:34, Issue 191, 1966 May 6 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- "Androgenic and Anabolic Hormones" 8:35, Issue 191, May 6, 1966 "Liver Injury and Anabolic-Androgenic Agents" 8:52, Issue 195, 1966 July 1; 1966 May 6 (Box 105, Folder 2-6)
- "Topical Corticosteroids for Skin Disorders" 8:37, Issue 192, 1966 May 20 (Box 105, Folder 7-9)
- "Adrenosem and Hemostasis" 8:39, Issue 192, 1966 May 20 (Box 105, Folder 10-12)
- "Chemotherapy in Severe Burns" 8:39, Issue 192, 1966 May 20 (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
- "Armour's 'Letter' for Hypothyroidism" 8:41, Issue 193, 1966 June 3 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- "Methotrexate for Psoriasis" 8:42, Issue 193, 1966 June 3 (Box 106, Folder 4-5)
- "Progestins in Habitual Abortion" 8:43, Issue 193, 1966 June 3 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- "Penicillin G-Resistant Staphylococcal Infections" 8:45, Issue 194, 1966 June 17 (Box 106, Folder 7-9)
- "A Drug to Induce Ovulation" 8:47, Issue 194, 1966 June 17 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
- "Clorpactin - An Antiseptic" 8:48, Issue 194, 1966 June 17 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- "Prevention of Indwelling Urinary Catheter Infections" 8:49, Issue 195, 1966 July 1 (Box 107, Folder 4-5)
- "Intersept Antiseptic Foam" 8:55, Issue 196, 1966 July 15 (Box 107, Folder 6-7)
- "Devices for Measuring Blood Volume" 8:56, Issue 196, 1966 July 15 (Box 107, Folder 8-10)
- "Choice of Antibacterial Drugs When Infecting Organisms Have Not Been Identified" 8:57, Issue 197, 1966 July 29 (Box 108, Folder 1-3)
- "Microorganisms Most Likely to Cause Infection" 8:60, Issue 197, 1966 July 29 (Box 108, Folder 4-5)
- "Ovulen - A New Oral Contraceptive" 8:61, Issue 198, 1966 August 12 (Box 108, Folder 6-8)
- "Stat-Test for Bacteriuria" 8:62, Issue 198, 1966 August 12 (Box 108, Folder 9-10)
- "Treatment of Respiratory Insufficiency" 8:63, Issue 198, 1966 August 12 (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
- "Clinical Significance of Serum Binding of Antibiotics" unpublished, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 5-6)
- "Panalba and Novobiocin" 8:65, Issue 199, 1966 August 26 (Box 109, Folder 7-8)
- "Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias Associated With Myocardial Infarction" 8:66, Issue 199, 1966 August 26 (Box 109, Folder 9-11)
- "The Choice of Therapy in the Treatment of Cancer" 8:69, Issue 200, 1966 September 9 (Box 110, Folder 1-6)
- "Tolinase - A New Oral Antidiabetic Drug" 8:77, Issue 201, 1966 September 23 (Box 110, Folder 7-8)
- "Influenza Immunization" 8:78, Issue 201, 1966 September 23 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- "Gonococcal Infections" 8:79, Issue 201, 1966 September 23 (Box 110, Folder 10, Box 111, Folder 1-2)
- "Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices" 8:81, Issue 202, 1966 October 7 (Box 111, Folder 3-7)
- "Nocturnal or Recumbency Muscle Cramps" 8:83, Issue 202, 1966 October 7 (Box 111, Folder 8-9)
- "Amniocentesis and Intrauterine Fetal Transfusion in Erythroblastosis Fetalis" 8:85, Issue 203, 1966 October 21 (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
- "Unopettes" 8:86, Issue 203, 1966 October 21 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
- "Anthraquinone Laxatives" 8:87, Issue 203, 1966 October 21 (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
- "Turbinaire" 8:89, Issue 204, 1966 November 4 (Box 112, Folder 6-7)
- "Trocinate and Valpin" 8:90, issue 204, 1966 November 4 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- "Determination of Ovulation Time and the Rhythm Method of Contraception" 8:91, Issue 204, 1966 November 4 (Box 112, Folder 9-10)
- "Rondomycin" 8:93, Issue 205, 1966 November 18 (Box 112, Folder 11, Box 113, Folder 1-2)
- "Sansert" 8:94, Issue 205, 1966 November 18 (Box 113, Folder 3-5)
- "Mono-Test" 8:95, Issue 205, 1966 November 18 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- "Citanest - A Local Anesthetic" 8:97, Issue 206, 1966 December 2 (Box 113, Folder 7-10)
- "Zyloprim and Other Drugs in the Management of Gout" 8:98, Issue 206, 1966 December 2 (Box 114, Folder 1-3)
- "Fluorescein Tests for Localizing Gastrointestinal Bleeding" 8:100, Issue 206, 1966 December 2 (Box 114, Folder 4-5)
- "A New Tetracycline Formulation" 8:101, Issue 207, 1966 December 16 (Box 114, Folder 6-9)
- "Detection of Proteinuria" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- "The Prevention of Urinary Calculi-I" 8:103, Issue 207, 1966 December 17 (Box 114, Folder 11-12, Box 115, Folder 1-4)
- "The Fogarty Catheterand Thromboembolism" 8:105, Issue 208, 1966 December 30 (Box 115, Folder 5-6)
- "Choice of Method for the Measurement of SGOT" 8:106, Issue 208, 1966 December 30 (Box 115, Folder 7-9)
- "LSD" 9:1, Issue 209, 1967 January 13 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- "Human Chorionic Gonadotropin (HCG) " 9:2, Issue 209, 1967 January 13 (Box 115, Folder 11, Box 116, Folder 1)
- "Newer Serum Enzyme Determinations as Aids in Diagnosis" 9:3, Issue 209, 1967 January 13 (Box 116, Folder 2-4)
- "Symmetrel - A New 'Antiviral' Agent" 9:5, Issue 210, 1967 January 27 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
- "Lasix" 9:6, Issue 210, 1967 January 27 (Box 116, Folder 7-11)
- "Cycloplasmol in Peripheral and Cerebral Vascular Disease" 9:9, Issue 211, 1967 February 10 (Box 116, Folder 12, Box 117, Folder 1-2)
- "Amicar and Hyperfibrinolysis" 9:10, Issue 211, 1967 February 10 (Box 117, Folder 3-8)
- "Dip Tests for Glycosuria" 9:12, Issue 211, 1967 February 10 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  {Note: 'Sources, Resources' material for 9:12 in box 180}.
- "Deprol Advertising" 9:13, Issue 212, 1967 February 24 (Box 117, Folder 10-11, Box 118, Folder 1-3)
- "Nitrofurazone - A Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:15, Issue 212, 1967 February 24 (Box 118, Folder 4-6)
- "Elase and Other Proteolytic Enzyme Drugs" 9:17, Issue 213, 1967 March 10 (Box 118, Folder 7-10, Box 119, Folder 1-2)
- "Bioplant" 9:18, Issue 213, March 10, 1967 "Surgibone (Bioplant) - Correction" 9:32, Issue 216, April 21, 1967, 1967 March 10; 1967 April 21 (Box 119, Folder 3-5)
- "Urography for Urea Nitrogen Determinations" 9:20, Issue 213, 1967 March 10 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- "Correction on Canadian Certification Procedures for Tetracyclines" 9:20, Issue 213, 1967 March 10 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- "The Choice of an Oral Contraceptive" 9:21, Issue 214, 1967 March 24 (Box 119, Folder 8-10)
- "Penthrane for Obstetrical Anesthesia" 9:23, Issue 214, 1967 March 24 (Box 119, Folder 11-12, Box 120, Folder 1-5)
- "Disinfection of Medical Equipment" 9:25, Issue 215, 1967 April 7 (Box 120, Folder 6-8)
- "Pipobroman (Vercyte) - A New Antineoplastic Drug" 9:27, Issue 215, 1967 April 7 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- "Cyproheptadine (Periactin) for Allergic and Pruritic Dermatoses" 9:28, Issue 215, 1967 April 7 (Box 120, Folder 10-11, Box 121, Folder 1)
- "Betahistine Hydrochloride (Serc) for Meniere's Syndrome" 9:29, Issue 216, 1967 April 21 (Box 121, Folder 2-4)
- "Antimicrobial Cold Remedies" 9:30, Issue 216, 1967 April 21 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- "Treatment of Hemorrhage in Hemophilia" 9:31, Issue 216, 1967 April 21 (Box 121, Folder 6-7)
- "Gentamicin (Garamycin) - A New Topical Antimicrobial Drug" 9:33, Issue 217, 1967 May 5 (Box 121, Folder 8-9)
- "Pheochromocytoma" 9:34, Issue 217, 1967 May 5 (Box 122, Folder 1-4)
- "Electrophoretic Studies as an Aid in Diagnosis" 9:36, Issue 217, 1967 May 5 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- "Fiorinal and Other Sedative-Analgesic Drugs for 'Tension' Headache" 9:37, Issue 218, 1967 May 19 (Box 122, Folder 6-7)
- "The Prevention and Medical Treatment of Urinary Calculi - II" 9:38, Issue 218, 1967 May 19 (Box 122, Folder 8-9)
- "Testuria for the Detection of Bacteriuria" 9:40, Issue 218, 1967 May 19 (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
- "Tests of Prednisone Tablets" 9:41, Issue 219, 1967 June 2 (Box 123, Folder 3-4)
- "Achilles Reflex Time in the Diagnosis of Thyroid Disfuction" 9:43, Issue 219, 1967 June 2 (Box 123, Folder 5-7)
- "Electrophoretic Studies as an Aid in Diagnosis - Correction" 9:44, Issue 219, 1967 June 2 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- "Atromid-S for the Reduction of Plasma Lipids" 9:45, Issue 220, 1967 June 16 (Box 123, Folder 9-11)
- "Effect of pH of the Urine on Antimicrobial Therapy of Urinary Tract Infections" 9:47, Issue 220, 1967 June 16 (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
- "Methotrimeprazine (Levoprome) - A Potent Analgesic" 9:49, Issue 221, 1967 June 30 (Box 124, Folder 4-8)
- "Penicillamine" 9:51, Issue 221, 1967 June 30 (Box 124, Folder 9-12)
- "Ethacrynic Acid" 9:53, Issue 222, 1967 July 14 (Box 125, Folder 1-3)
- "Penicillin G and Other Penicillins in the Treatment of Coccal Infections" 9:55, Issue 222, 1967 July 14 (Box 125, Folder 4-6)
- "Peritoneal Dialysis" 9:57, Issue 223, 1967 July 28 (Box 125, Folder 7-10, Box 126, Folder 1)
- "Drugs and Other Factors Interfering With Reliability of Blood Chemistry Determination" 9:59, Issue 223, 1967 July 28 (Box 126, Folder 2-3)
- "Kanamycin and Neomycin" 9:61, Issue 224, 1967 August 11 (Box 126, Folder 4-7)
- "Diphenylhydrantoin (Dilantin) in Cardiac Arrhythmias" 9:64, Issue 224, 1967 August 11 (Box 126, Folder 8)
- "Chlorphenesin Carbamate (Maolate) " 9:65, Issue 225, 1967 August 25 (Box 126, Folder 9-10)
- "Serum Bactericidal Test in Bacterial Endocarditis and Bacteremias" 9:66, Issue 225, 1967 August 25 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- "Incompatability of Drugs for Intravenous Administration" 9:67, Issue 225, 1967 August 25 (Box 127, Folder 2-3)
- "Treatment of Atypical Pneumonia" 9:69, Issue 226, 1967 September 8 (Box 127, Folder 4-6)
- "Haloperidol" 9:70, Issue 226, 1967 September 8 (Box 127, Folder 7-10, Box 128, Folder 1-2)
- "Hypersensitivity Skin Reactions due to Neomycin" 9:71, Issue 226, 1967 September 8 (Box 128, Folder 3-6)
- "Marijuana" 9:73 "A Note on STP" 9:74, Issue 227, 1967 September 22 (Box 128, Folder 7-9)
- "Tinver Lotion and Other Topical Preparations for Tinea Versicolor" 9:74, Issue 227, 1967 September 22 (Box 128, Folder 10-11)
- "Mefenamic Acid (Ponstel) " 9:77, Issue 228, 1967 October 6 (Box 129, Folder 1-8)
- "Ampicillin" 9:78, Issue 228, 1967 October 6 (Box 129, Folder 9, Box 130, Folder 1-3)
- "Influenza Immunization" 9:81, Issue 229, 1967 October 20 (Box 130, Folder 4-6)
- "Effects of Drugs on the PBI and T3 Uptake" 9:82, Issue 229, 1967 October 20 (Box 130, Folder 7-10)
- "Transfusion of Blood Components (Part I) " 9:85, Issue 230, 1967 November 3 (Box 131, Folder 1-10)
- "Diphenidol (Vontrol) " 9:91, Issue 231, 1967 November 17 (Box 132, Folder 1-5)
- "Penicillamine" 5:64, Issue 119, 1963 August 2 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- "Adverse Effects of Topical Antiglaucoma Drugs" 9:92, Issue 231, 1967 November 17 (Box 132, Folder 7-10, Box 133, Folder 1-2)
- "Magnesium - Its Nutritional and Pharmacologic Effects" 9:93, Issue 231, 1967 November 17 (Box 133, Folder 3-6)
- "Pentazocine (Talwin) " 9:95, Issue 232, 1967 December 1 (Box 133, Folder 7-10)
- "Interactions of Oral Anticoagulants With Other Drugs" 9:97, Issue 232, 1967 December 1 (Box 134, Folder 1-4)
- "Hepatic Coma and Exchange Transfusion" 9:98, Issue 232, 1967 December 1 (Box 134, Folder 5-8)
- "Thiabendazole (Mintezol) - A New Anthelmintic" 9:99, Issue 233, 1967 December 15 (Box 134, Folder 9-12)
- "Corticosteroid Enemas for Ulcerative Colitis" 9:102, Issue 233, 1967 December 15 (Box 135, Folder 1-4)
- "Sodium Dextrothyroxine (Choloxin) " 9:103, Issue 234, 1967 December 29 (Box 135, Folder 5-11, Box 136, Folder 1-2)
- "Duration of Antibacterial Therapy" 9:104, Issue 234, 1967 December 29 (Box 136, Folder 3-6)
- "Thiothixene (Navane) - Another Antipsychotic Drug" 10:1, Issue 235, 1968 January 12 (Box 136, Folder 7-9)
- "Azostix for Determining Blood Urea Nitrogen (BUN) " 10:2, Issue 235, 1968 January 12 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- "Dextran 40 and Other Dextrans" 10:3, Issue 235, 1968 January 12 (Box 137, Folder 1-7)
- "Mannitol - An Osmotic Diuretic" 10:5, Issue 236, 1968 January 26 (Box 137, Folder 8-11, Box 138, Folder 1)
- "Treatment of Malaria" 10:6, Issue 236, 1968 January 26 (Box 138, Folder 2-3)
- "Halothane and Liver Injury" 10:7, Issue 236, 1968 January 26 (Box 138, Folder 4-8)
- "Requiem for Flavonid Drugs" 10:9, Issue 237, 1968 February 9 (Box 138, Folder 9, Box 139, Folder 1-4)
- "Hodgkin's Disease" 10:10, Issue 237, 1968 February 9 (Box 139, Folder 5-7)
- "Doxycycline (Vibramycin) " 10:13, Issue 238, 1968 February 23 (Box 139, Folder 8-11)
- "Mumps Virus Vaccine" 10:14, Issue 238, 1968 February 23 (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
- "The Unitest System" 10:15, Issue 238, 1968 February 23 (Box 140, Folder 4-5)
- "Protriptyline (Vivactil) - Another Antidepressant" 10:17, Issue 239, 1968 March 8 (Box 140, Folder 6-11)
- "Vi-Penta and 'Vertical Deficiency'" 10:18, Issue 239, 1968 March 8 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- "Vaginostic Diagnostic Kit" 10:19, Issue 239, 1968 March 8 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- "Adverse Ophthalmic Effects of Corticosteroids" 10:21, Issue 240, 1968 March 22 (Box 141, Folder 3-5)
- "Adverse Effects of Methyldopa" 10:22, Issue 240, 1968 March 22 (Box 141, Folder 6-8)
- "Acne Vulgaris - Guidelines for Treatment" 10:23, Issue 240, 1968 March 22 (Box 141, Folder 9-10, Box 142, Folder 1-2)
- "Adr. Cort. Hormones (Medrysone) [Manufacturer's Information]" Unpublished (?), 1968 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- "Propranolol" 10:25, Issue 241, 1968 April 5 (Box 142, Folder 4-8)
- "Allergic Contact Dermatitis to Parabens" 10:27, Issue 241, 1968 April 5 (Box 142, Folder 9-10)
- "Intra-Auricular Administration of Corticosteroids" 10:31, Issue 242, 1968 April 19 (Box 143, Folder 1-4)
- "Photosensitivity to Systemic and Topical Drugs" 10:32, Issue 242, 1968 April 19 (Box 143, Folder 5-6)
- "Chloramphenicol" 10:33, Issue 243, 1968 May 3 (Box 143, Folder 7-8)
- "Drug Combinations for Primary Hypertension" 10:34, Issue 243, 1968 May 3 (Box 143, Folder 9-10, Box 144, Folder 1-3)
- "Hirsutism" 10:36, Issue 243, 1968 May 3 (Box 144, Folder 4-6)
- "Indomethacin (Indocin) " 10:37, Issue 244, 1968 May 17 (Box 144, Folder 7-10, Box 145, Folder 1)
- "Diarrhea Caused by Shigella" 10:38, Issue 244, May 17, 1968 "Salmonella Infections" 10:50, Issue 247, 1968 May 17; 1968 June 28 (Box 145, Folder 2-7)
- "Intravenous Alcohol in Premature Labor" 10:40, Issue 244, 1968 May 17 (Box 145, Folder 8-9)
- "Ethambutol Hydrochloride (Myambutol) " 10:41, Issue 245, 1968 May 31 (Box 145, Folder 10-11, Box 146, Folder 1-3)
- "Particulate Matter in Parenteral Solutions" 10:42, Issue 245, 1968 May 31 (Box 146, Folder 4-7)
- "Cure of Vivax Malaria" 10:44, Issue 245, 1968 May 31 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- "Cephaloridine (Loridine) " 10:45, Issue 246, 1968 June 14 (Box 146, Folder 9-11, Box 147, Folder 1-2)
- "Parenteral Multivitamins for the Surgical Patient" 10:46, Issue 246, 1968 June 14 (Box 147, Folder 3-5)
- "Insect Sting Allergy" 10:47, Issue 246, 1968 June 14 (Box 147, Folder 6-9)
- "Carbamazepine (Tegretol) " 10:49, Issue 247, 1968 June 28 (Box 147, Folder 10, Box 148, Folder 1-4)
- "Home Hemodialysis" 10:53, Issue 248, 1968 July 12 (Box 148, Folder 5-7)
- "Electrofulguration for Varicose Veins" 10:54, Issue 248, 1968 July 12 (Box 148, Folder 8-10)
- "Insect Repellents" 10:55, Issue 248, 1968 July 12 (Box 148, Folder 11, Box 149, Folder 1-2)
- "Continuous Versus Intermittent Intravenous Antibiotics" 10:57, Issue 249, 1968 July 26 (Box 149, Folder 3-5)
- "Methenamine Hippurate (Hiprex)" 10:58, Issue 249, 1968 July 26 (Box 149, Folder 6-8)
- "Bephenium Hydroxynaphthoate (Alcopara)" 10:60, Issue 249, 1968 July 26 (Box 149, Folder 9-10)
- "Sulfameter (Sulla) - A Long-Acting Sulfonamide" 10:61, Issue 250, 1968 August 9 (Box 150, Folder 1-5)
- "Dicloxacillin - A New Penicillinase-Resistant Penicillin" 10:65, Issue 251, 1968 August 23 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  {Note: more in box 173}
- "Oral Contraceptives" 10:66, Issue 251, 1968 August 23 (Box 150, Folder 7-11, Box 151, Folder 1-3)
- "New and Old Drugs for Parkinsonism" 10:69, Issue 252, 1968 September 6 (Box 151, Folder 4-8)
- "Hydroxyurea (Hydrea) " 10:72, Issue 252, 1968 September 6 (Box 151, Folder 9, Box 152, Folder 1-3)
- "Principle Toxic, Allergic, and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" 10:73, Issue 253, 1969 September 20 (Box 152, Folder 4-9)
- "The Choice of Systemic Antimicrobial Drugs" 10:77, Issue 254, 1968 October 4 (Box 152, Folder 10, Box 153, Folder 1-5)
- "Diagnostest" 10:85, Issue 255, 1968 October 18 (Box 153, Folder 6-7)
- "Portagen" 10:87, Issue 255, 1968 October 18 (Box 153, Folder 8-10, Box 154, Folder 1-3)
- "Butaperazine (Repoise) " 10:89, Issue 256, 1968 November 1 (Box 154, Folder 4-5)
- "Radioactive Isotope Scanning" 10:90, Issue 256, 1968 November 1 (Box 154, Folder 6-9, Box 155, Folder 1-2)
- "Influenza Immunization" 10:92, Issue 256, 1968 November 1 (Box 155, Folder 3-4)
- "Exercise and Coronary Heart Disease" 10:93, Issue 257, 1968 November 15 (Box 155, Folder 5-10, Box 156, Folder 1)
- "RhoGAM - Anti-Rho (D) Immune Globulin" 10:94, Issue 257, 1968 November 15 (Box 156, Folder 2-6)
- "Sodium Colistimethate (Coly-Mycin) " 10:96, Issue 257, 1968 November 15 (Box 156, Folder 7-8)
- "Drugs Influencing Sexual Desire and Performance" 5:45, Issue 115, 1963 June 7 (Box 156, Folder 9-10)
- "Afrodex and Impotence" 10:97, Issue 258, 1968 November 29 (Box 156, Folder 11)
- "Treatment of Pneumocystis carnii Pneumonia" 10:98, Issue 258, 1968 November 29 (Box 157, Folder 1-3)